Guide to the Wade Hall 8 track tapes PM.012
University Libraries Division of Special Collections, The University of Alabama
- Box 18
  - Elvis: a legendary performer vol. 1 - RCA, 1973. (CPS1-0341) (Box 18)
  - The Great Mel Tillis - Gusto Records, 1979. (GT8-0047) (Box 18)
  - Still Crazy After All These Years - Paul Simon - Columbia, 1975. (PCA 33540) (Box 18)
  - The Best of Buck Owens- Capitol Records/RCA, no date. (S 123871), n.d. (Box 18)
  - Love It To Death - Alice Cooper - no info., n.d. (Box 18)
  - One Nation Under A Groove - Funkadelic - Warner Bros, 1978. (WB M8 3209) (Box 18)
  - Do It All Night - Curtis Mayfield - Curtom Records, 1978. (M8U 5022) (Box 18)
  - Wizzard introducing Eddy and the Falcons - Warner Bros, 1974. (K856029) (Box 18)
  - Memories - Bonnie Bramlett - Capricorn Records, 1978. (M8N-0199) (Box 18)
  - Sumner - Elektra/Asylum, 1980. (ET-8266) (Box 18)
  - Mirror - Graham Central Station - Warner Bros, 1976. (Box 18)
- Box 19
  - The Souther, Hillman, Furay Band - Asylum, 1974., 2.0 (Box 19)
  - From the Inside - Alice Cooper - Warner Bros. 1978. (WB M 8 3263) (Box 19)
  - Two Sides of the Moon - Keith Moon - Track Records, 1975. (MCAT-2136) (Box 19)
  - Mirror - Graham Central Station - Warner Bros., 1976. (M 8 2937) (Box 19)
  - I Reserve the Right - Stillwater - Capricorn Records, 1978. (M8N-0210) (Box 19)
  - Bama Ray Plays Country - Custom Recording, 1974. (Box 19)
  - Anvil Chorus - The Kids - ATCO Records, 1975. (ATC TP 36-114 0797) (Box 19)
  - White Night - Michael White - Elektra/Asylum, 1979. (ET-8183) (Box 19)
  - The Inside Story - Robben Ford - Elektra/Asylum, 1979. (ET-8169) (Box 19)
  - Pratt & McClain featuring "Happy Days" - Reprise/RCA Music Service edition, 1976. (M8-2250) (Box 19)
  - Innuendo - Danny Kortchmar- Elektra/Asylum, 1980. (ET-8250) (Box 19)
  - Another Year - Leo Sayer - Warner Bros., 1975. (WB M8 2885) (Box 19)
  - Playing My fiddle For You - Papa John Creach and Zulu - Grunt Records, 1974. (BFS1-0418) (Box 19)
  - Heads - Bob James - Columbia House/Tappan Zee, 1977. (JCA 34896) (Box 19)
  - Cooper Brothers - Capricorn Records, 1978. (M8N-0206) (Box 19)
- Box 20
  - Memories - Bonnie Bramlett - Capricorn Records, 1978. (M8N-0199), 3.0 (Box 20)
  - Mirror - Graham Central Station - Warner Bros., 1976. (0797), 6.0 (Box 20)
  - One Nation Under a Groove - Funkadelic - Warner Bros., 1978. (M8 3209), 3.0 (Box 20)
  - Hardcore Jollies - Funkadelic - Warner Bros., 1976. (M8 2973), 2.0 (Box 20)
  - Good Singin' Good Playin'- Grand Funk Railroad - MCA, 1976. (MCAT-2216), 2.0 (Box 20)
- Box 21
  - Cooper Brothers - Capricorn Records, 1978. (M8N-0206), 2.0 (Box 21)
  - The Inside Story - Robben Ford - Elektra/Asylum, 1979. (ET-8169), 3.0 (Box 21)
  - Get It On - Pacific Gas & Electric - no date. (8547), n.d. (Box 21)
  - Fly Away - Voyage - Marlin Records, 1978. (2225) (Box 21)
  - Dedication - Bay City Rollers - Arista Records, 1976. (4093 H) (Box 21)
  - Make Love to the Music - Leon & Mary Russell- Paradise Records, 1977. (Box 21)
  - Muhammad Ali - the Greatest - an original soundtrack - Arista/Warner, 1977. (M8 3069) (Box 21)
  - Rough Diamond - Island Records, 1977. (Y8I-9490) (Box 21)
  - Time Fades Away - Neil Young - Reprise Records, 1973. (0697) (Box 21)
  - Fire On Ice - Terry Callier - Elektra/Asylum, 1978. (ET-8143) (Box 21)
  - Nobody's Blues But Mine vol. 2 - Bessie Smith - no date. (581), n.d. (Box 21)
  - From the Inside - Alice Cooper - Warner Bros., 1978. (M8 3263) (Box 21)
  - Ooh, La, La - Suzi Lane - Elektra/Asylum, 1979. (ET-8207) (Box 21)
- Box 22
  - John Fogerty - Asylum Records, 1975. (ET-81046) (Box 22)
  - Funk Factory - ATCO Records, 1975. (TP 36-116 0797) (Box 22)
  - Between the Lines - Bobby Braddock - Elektra/Asylum, 1979. (ET-8187), 2.0 (Box 22)
  - Valli - Frankie Valli - Private Stock Records, 1976. (8300-2017 H) (Box 22)
  - Arabesque - John Klemmer - ABC Records, 1978. (8020 AA-1068 H0 (Box 22)
  - David Sanborn - Warner Bros., 1976. (2957) (Box 22)
  - Young and In Love - Stacy Lattisaw - Atlantic, 1979. (TP 5214), 2.0 (Box 22)
  - Duo Glide - Sanford and Townsend - Warner Bros., 1977. (MB 3081), 3.0 (Box 22)
  - Nightingale - Gilberto Gil - Elektra/Asylum, 1979. (ET-8167), 2.0 (Box 22)
  - Voyager - Karen Alexander - Elektra/Asylum, 1978. (ET-8130), 2.0 (Box 22)
- Box 23
  - Mirror - Graham Central Station - Warner Bros., 1976. (M8 2937), 2.0 (Box 23)
  - Gate of Dreams - Claus Ogerman Orchestra - Warner Bros., 1977. (M8 3006), 2.0 (Box 23)
  - Memories - Bonnie Bramlett - Capricorn Records, 1978. (M8N-0199), 2.0 (Box 23)
  - Cooper Brothers - Capricorn, 1978. (M8N-0206), 3.0 (Box 23)
  - Dark Lady - Cher - MCA, 1974. (MCAT-2113) (Box 23)
  - Smoke From a Distant Fire - Sanford and Townsend - Warner Bros, 1976. (Box 23)
  - Bread and Roses - Judy Collins - Elektra/Asylum, 1976. (ET-81076) (Box 23)
  - Cherries, Bananas, and Other Fine Things -Jeannie Reynolds - Casablanca Records, 1976. (NBLP-87029) (Box 23)
  - So Soon We Change - David Ruffin - Warner Bros, 1979. (Box 23)
  - Turn Me Loose - Sweetbottom - Elektra/Asylum, 1979. (Box 23)
  - One Nation Under a Groove - Funkadelic - Warner Bros., 1978. (Box 23)
- Box 24
  - Roots - Curtis Mayfield - Bonanza, no date. ( 513), n.d. (Box 24)
  - Excerpts from the rock musical "Godspell" - Pickwick, 1973. (P8-1185) (Box 24)
  - Echoes of an Era - Duke Ellington & Louis Armstrong - Bonanza, no date. (590), n.d. (Box 24)
  - Sumner - Elektra/Asylum, 1980. (ET-8266) (Box 24)
  - Pass It On - The Staples - Warner Bros, 1976. (M8 2945) (Box 24)
  - The Inside Story - Robben Ford - Elektra/Asylum, 1979. (ET-8169) (Box 24)
  - Fly With Me - Supermax - Elektra/Asylum, 1979. (ET-8193) (Box 24)
  - Randy Meisner - Elektra/Asylum, 1978. (ET-8140) (Box 24)
  - Rough Diamond - Island, 1977. (Y8I-9490) (Box 24)
  - The Best On Record! - various artists - Columbia, no date. (CA 10180), n.d. (Box 24)
  - Four & More - Miles Davis - no date. (178), n.d. (Box 24)
  - The Rutles - Warner Bros, 1978. (W8 3151) (Box 24)
  - Dixieland - Pete Fountain and other All-star Dixielanders - RCA, no date. (C8S 1050) (Box 24)
  - Whirlwinds - Deodato - MCA, 1974. (MCAT-410) (Box 24)
  - Walking Man - James Taylor - Warner Bros, 1974. (L8W 2794) (Box 24)
  - Kings of Dixieland - Vogue, no date. (Box 24)
- Box 25
  - Let's Keep It That Way - Anne Murray - Capitol, 1978. (8XT 511743) (Box 25)
  - Barry Manilow II - Bell Records, 1974. (8301-1314) (Box 25)
  - Golden Hits of the King (Elvis Presley) - collector's edition vol. 1 - PPI, 1977. (1096) (Box 25)
  - Long Ago and Far Away - The Great Love Songs of the 40's - Columbia/CBS, 1974. (1A2 6264 vol. 1) (1A1 6265 vol. 2), 2.0 items (Box 25)
  - Steppenwolf 16 Greatest Hits - ABC Records, 1973. (M 8023-50135) (Box 25)
  - Welcome - Santana - Columbia/CBS, 1973. (PCA 32445) (Box 25)
  - Simon and Garfunkel's Greatest Hits - Columbia/CBS, 1972. (CA 31350) (Box 25)
  - I Got a Name - Jim Croce - ABC Records, 1973. (M 8022-797) (Box 25)
  - Very Best of Neil Diamond - Bang Records, no date. (8011-1001) (Box 25)
  - Spirit of America - Beach Boys - Capitol, 1975. (8XWW 511384) (Box 25)
  - Hank Williams, Sr. Live At the Grand Ole Opry - MGM, 1976. (S 124219) (Box 25)
  - Hello, Dolly! - Louis Armstrong - Lyric, no date. (LA 1212), n.d. (Box 25)
  - Today's Super Stars - Columbia, no date. (CA 10177), n.d. (Box 25)
  - Charge! Enoch Light & The Light Brigade - Project 3, no date. ( PRQ8-5073), n.d. (Box 25)
  - Christmas in my Home Town - Charley Pride - RCA, 1970. (P8S-1618) (Box 25)
  - Leave Your Sorrows and Come Along with the Happy Goodmans - Canaan/Word Inc., 1972. (3-9706) (Box 25)
- Box 26
  - Best of Dolly Parton - RCA, 1975. (APS1-1117) (Box 26)
  - Chet Atkins Picks on the Hits - RCA, 1972. (P8S-2018) (Box 26)
  - Maynard Ferguson - M.F. Horn 13 - CBS, 1973. (CA 32403) (Box 26)
  - Get Ready - Rare Earth - no date. (RAR M 8507), n.d. (Box 26)
  - Two Guns - Balls Out - Capricorn, 1979. (M8N-0224) (Box 26)
  - Two Sides of the Moon - Keith Moon - MCA, 1975. (MCAT-2136) (Box 26)
  - Roger Williams Greatest Hits - Kapp Records, no date. (K8 3260), n.d. (Box 26)
  - Don't Shoot Me, I'm Only the Piano Player - Elton John - MCA, 1972. (MCT0 2100) (Box 26)
  - There with You - AC Retailer - Columbia, no date. (CA 10292), n.d. (Box 26)
  - It's Too Late - Ferrante & Teicher - United Artists, no date. ( 8 U-8297), n.d. (Box 26)
  - Do It! - Neil Diamond - no date. (Box 26)
  - The New Sound of Today - various artists, Columbia, no date. (CA 10178) (Box 26)
  - For All We Know - Charlie Byrd - no date. (577), n.d. (Box 26)
  - Rock Volume "511" various artists, Hit Records, no date. (R1269), n.d. (Box 26)
  - Ramblin' Rose - Nat King Cole - Capitol, no date. (8XT 1793), n.d. (Box 26)
  - This Is the Moody Blues part one - The Moody Blues - Threshold Records, 1974. (THI 00812) (Box 26)
  - More of the Fifties Greatest Love Songs/Golden Hits - Columbia, no date. (68 20 0322), n.d. (Box 26)
- Box 27
  - Cadillac 1979 - The Beautiful Sound of Contemporary Music - RCA, 1978. (DAS2-0338) (Box 27)
  - Halfway Hotel - Voyager - Elektra/Asylum, 1979. (ET-8208) (Box 27)
  - Music from "The Sound of Music" - Living Strings - RCA, no date. (C8S 1006) (Box 27)
  - A Time for Love - Bobby Hackett with strings - Project 3, no date. (M 85016), n.d. (Box 27)
  - Parallel Lines - Blondie - Chrysalis Records, 1978. (8CH 1192) (Box 27)
  - Mel Street's Greatest Hits - GRT, no date. (8185-8010 H), n.d. (Box 27)
  - 200 Years of American Music - Lawrence Welk - GRT, 1975. (8058-7002N) (Box 27)
  - Songs in the Key of Life - Stevie Wonder - Motown, 1976. (T15-340 ET vol. 1) (Box 27)
  - Healing - Jimmy Swaggart - Jim Records, 1982. (JIM 139) (Box 27)
  - Dawn's New Ragtime Follies featuring Tony Orlando - Bell Records, 1973. (830 14008) (Box 27)
  - Today's Super Greats - various artists - K-tel, 1973. (TU-231-8ST-1) (Box 27)
  - 'S Marvelous -Ray Connif and his Orchestra - Columbia, no date. (LEA 10002) (Box 27)
  - Profile - Best of Emmylou Harris - Warner Bros, 1978. (M8 3258) (Box 27)
  - Going For the One - Yes - Atlantic, 1977. (TP 19106) (Box 27)
  - A Brand New Me - Dusty Springfield - Atlantic, no date. (M 88240) (Box 27)
  - The Ohio Players - Up Front Records, no date. (8T-UPF-167), n.d. (Box 27)
  - Country Cassanova - Commander Cody - Paramount, 1973. (M 8091-6054) (Box 27)
- Box 28
  - Blondes Have More Fun - Rod Stewart - Warner Bros. no date. (M8 3261) (Box 28)
  - Music of Love - Richard Clayderman - CBS, 1984. (BA-17661) (Box 28)
  - Eve - The Alan Parsons Project - Arista, 1979. (AT8 9504) (Box 28)
  - Great Contemporary Instrumental Hits - Ray Conniff - Columbia, no date. (CA 30755), n.d. (Box 28)
  - Don't Say No - Billy Squier - Capitol, 1981. (8XT-12146) (Box 28)
  - "The Sting" original motion picture soundtrack featuring the music of Scott Joplin - MCA, 1974. (MCAT 390) (Box 28)
  - The Best of Wayne Newton Live - Chelsea Record Corp., 1974. (CHF 8504) (Box 28)
  - Go For the Night - Freddy Weller - CBS/Columbia, 1980. (JCA 36231) (Box 28)
  - The Best of Guy Lombardo and The Royal Canadians vol. 2 - Capitol, no date. (8XT 502940) (Box 28)
  - Engelbert Humperdinck - His Greatest Hits - Decca, 1974. (PF8 71067) (Box 28)
  - The Entertainer - Roy Clark - DOT Records, 1974. (8150-2001) (Box 28)
  - Paint Your Wagon - music from the soundtrack - Paramount, no date. (PM 89004) (Box 28)
  - Just Good Ol' Boys - Moe Bandy & Joe Stampley - CBS, 1979. (JCA 36202) (Box 28)
  - Behind Closed Doors - Charlie Rich - CBS, 1973. (PEA 32247) (Box 28)
  - Hits of (Crash) Craddock & Jim Ed Brown - Eagle Records, no date. (E 239), n.d. (Box 28)
  - The Barons at the Heidelberg - Sound Records, no date. (1098-8) (Box 28)
  - Candy-O - The Cars - Elektra/Asylum, 1979. (5T-8507) (Box 28)
- Box 29
  - Live Cream vol. 2 - Atlantic, 1972. (TP-7005) (Box 29)
  - Roberta Flack & Donny Hathaway - Atlantic, 1972. (M 87216) (Box 29)
  - Songs from the Wood - Jethro Tull - Chrysalis, 1977. (8CH 1132) (Box 29)
  - Anyone Who Had a Heart - Dionne Warwick - Scepter Records, no date. (TSPS517), n.d. (Box 29)
  - Seventh Sojourn - The Moody Blues - London, no date. (M 24807) (Box 29)
  - Crimes of Passion - Pat Benatar - Chrysalis, 1980. (8CE 1275) (Box 29)
  - New Riders of the Purple Sage - Marin County Line - MCA, 1977. (MCAT 2307) (Box 29)
  - Ballad of a Teenage Queen - Johnny Cash - Koala Records, 1981. (Box 29)
  - Diesel On My Tail - Jim & Jesse - no date. (620), n.d. (Box 29)
  - Close To You - The Carpenters - Masterphonic Sounds, no date. (CP-105) (Box 29)
  - Earth - Jefferson Starship - Grunt Records, 1978. (BXS1-2515) (Box 29)
  - 100 World's Most Beautiful Melodies - tape 1 - Reader's Digest - no date. (SMI 8-89), n.d. (Box 29)
  - The 12 Days of Christmas - Pickwick, 1976. (P8-1021) (Box 29)
  - The Grassroots - Their 16 Greatest Hits - no date. (193), n.d. (Box 29)
  - One of a Kind - Moe Bandy - CBS, 1979. (JCA 36228) (Box 29)
  - Diana Ross and The Supremes Greatest Hits - Motown, no date. (MOT-8 2663) (Box 29)
  - The First Time Ever (I Saw Your Face) - Vikki Carr - CBS. 1972. (CA 31453) (Box 29)
- Box 30
  - #1 Hit Parade vol. 5 & 6 - Columbia House/CBS, 1978. (A23 6845) (Box 30)
  - Tommy - The Who - Decca Records, no date. (6-2500), n.d. (Box 30)
  - Eddie Money - no info. (PCA 34909), n.d. (Box 30)
  - World of Boots Randolph - Monument Records, 1972. (30963-8) (Box 30)
  - Body and Soul of Tom Jones - no info. (1184) (Box 30)
  - Bobbie Gentry & Glen Campbell - Masterphonic Sounds, no date. ( GC-382) (Box 30)
  - Big Brother and the Holding Company - Cheap Thrills - Columbia, no date. (180 HO 0488) (Box 30)
  - Best of Willie Nelson - United Artists, 1973. (UA-EA 086G) (Box 30)
  - Best of Glenn Miller (tape 1) - BMG Music, 1987. (DVS2-0810) (Box 30)
  - Feelings - various artists - 1977. (8035-1) (Box 30)
  - Truth of Truths - a contemporary rock opera - vol. 2 - Oak Records, no date. (T8139-1001), n.d. (Box 30)
  - But the Little Girls Understand - The Knack - Capitol Records, 1980. (8XOO-12045) (Box 30)
  - Tea for the Tillerman - Cat Stevens - no info., n.d. (Box 30)
  - Music Chart Busters - various artists - vol. 7 - Columbia House/CBS, no date. (1A1 6846), n.d. (Box 30)
  - Jazz - Queen - Elektra/Asylum, 1978. (ET-8166) (Box 30)
  - Look of Love - vol. 4 - Columbia Musical Treasury - no date. (68 20 0070), n.d. (Box 30)
  - On the Radio - Donna Summer Greatest Hits - Casablanca, 1979. (NBLB 7191/2) (Box 30)
- Box 31
  - Heaven's Just a Sin Away - The Kendalls - Ovation, 1976. (Box 31)
  - Love Rock - various artists - Ronco, 1977. (PA 14235) (Box 31)
  - Puccini's Greatest Hits - RCA, 1971. (R8S-1195) (Box 31)
  - Lawrence Welk celebrates 25 years on television - Ranwood/Teleklew, 1975. (Box 31)
  - Lefty Frizell's Greatest Hits - Lyric, no date. (C-3033), n.d. (Box 31)
  - Simon and Garfunkel's Greatest Hits - CBS, 1972. (CA 31350) (Box 31)
  - The Country America Loves - The Statler Brothers - Mercury/RCA, 1977. (S 150083) (Box 31)
  - Magic of Arthur Fielder and the Boston Pops - vol. II - Polygram, 1979. (SP8-105) (Box 31)
  - Blackwood Brothers Live from Nashville - Skylite Records, no date. (SLP-6173) Signed by members, n.d. (Box 31)
  - Fiddler on the Roof - original broadway cast recording - RCA, 1964. (O8S-1005) (Box 31)
  - Who's Gonna Play That Old Piano - Jerry Lee Lewis - Mercury, no date. (MC-8-61366), n.d. (Box 31)
  - More Mantovani Golden Hits - Mantovani and his orchestra - London Records/RCA, 1976. (PS8 914) (Box 31)
  - Sacred Strings of Jimmy Swaggart - Jim Records, 1972. (Shiloh 6000) (Box 31)
  - Quiet Fire - Roberta Flack - Atlantic, no date. (ATL M 81594), n.d. (Box 31)
  - Passin' the Faith Along - The Gaither Vocal Band - Benson Company/Word Records, 1983. (4-4102) (Box 31)
  - Pat Boone Family - Word Records, no date. (2-8536), n.d. (Box 31)
  - With Love, Marty Robbins - RCA, no date. (C980), n.d. (Box 31)
- Box 32
  - Easy to Remember - Terry Baxter, his orchestra and chorus - volumes 1-3 - Columbia Musical Treasury - no date., 3.0 items (Box 32)
  - 120 Music Masterpieces Highlights - volume 1-3 - Columbia Musical Treasury - no date., n.d.; 3.0 items (Box 32)
  - Doctor Zhivago sound track - MGM, no date. (8130-6) (Box 32)
  - 24 of Hank Williams' Greatest Hits - MGM, no date. (MGJ 84755), n.d. (Box 32)
  - Juanita Hall Sings the Blues - Cassette Music, no date. (8112), n.d. (Box 32)
  - Coal Miner's Daughter - Loretta Lynn - no info. (471), n.d. (Box 32)
  - If You Want It, I Got It - Johnny Rivers - Capitol/Pickwick, no date. (P8-182), n.d. (Box 32)
  - Bridge Over Troubled Water - Ray Conniff- Columbia, no date. (18 10 1022), n.d. (Box 32)
  - Joseph and the Amazing Technicolor Dreamcoat - The Joseph Consortium - Scepter Records, no date. (TSPS 588) (Box 32)
  - Mud Slide Slim and the Blue Horizon - James Taylor - Warner Bros, no date. (8WM-2561) (Box 32)
  - Whales & Nightingales - Judy Collins - Elektra, no date. (ET8-5010), n.d. (Box 32)
  - Mississippi Talkin - Jerry Clower from Yazoo City - Colorado Music Co., no date., n.d. (Box 32)
- Box 33
  - Rachmaninoff's Piano Concerto - featuring Steve Blaine's Piano and Orchestra - no info. (8T 2028) (Box 33)
  - Folsom Prison Blues - various artists - Country Road, (CR 8T 44), n.d. (Box 33)
  - Songs of the Depression - Happy Days Are Here Again - CBS/Book-of-the-Month Records, 1980. (Box 33)
  - I'm Gonna Be A Country Girl Again - Buffy Sainte-Marie - Vanguard, no date. (VGM-89280), n.d. (Box 33)
  - A Tramp Shining - Richard Harris - Dunhill/ABC Records, no date. (823-50032), n.d. (Box 33)
  - Astounding 12-string Guitar of Glen Campbell - Capitol, no date. (8XT 2023) (Box 33)
  - The Legendary Woody Guthrie - In Memoriam - Tradition - no date. (859-2058) (Box 33)
  - Swing Low Sweet Chariot - B.B. King - Cadet Records, no date. (815-116), n.d. (Box 33)
  - Fiddlin' Country Style - Tommy Jackson, Benny Martin & Others - Country Road, no date. (CR-8T-103), n.d. (Box 33)
  - Blessed Are... Joan Baez - Vanguard - no date. (VGJ 86570), n.d. (Box 33)
  - Bernstein Conducts Wagner - New York Philharmonic - Columbia - no date. (MA 31011) (Box 33)
  - Best of '69 - Terry Baxter and his orchestra - Columbia, no date. (68 20 0132) (Box 33)
  - Liberace - My Most Requested - Paramount, no date. (PA 81089), n.d. (Box 33)
  - Fiddler on the Roof - original Broadway cast recording - RCA, no date. (O8S 1005), n.d. (Box 33)
  - HAIR - original Broadway cast recording - RCA, no date. (O8S 1038), n.d. (Box 33)
  - Bridge Over Troubled Water - Simon and Garfunkel - Columbia, no date. (18 10 0750) (Box 33)
- Box 34
  - Talk It Over In the Morning - Anne Murray - Capitol, no date. (8XT 821), n.d. (Box 34)
  - Elvis Sings Songs of Christmas - RCA, no date. (P8S 1249), n.d. (Box 34)
  - Mahler: Symphony no.1 - Boston Symphony/Leinsdorf, RCA, 1963. (R8S 1080) (Box 34)
  - Best of Arthur Fiedler and the Boston Pops - RCA, 1965. (R8S 1047) (Box 34)
  - Close Up - Tom Jones - London/Decca, 1972. (PEM 79855) (Box 34)
  - Performance - original motion picture soundtrack - starring James Fox - Mick Jagger - Warner Bros, no date. (M 82554) (Box 34)
  - Filles de Kilimanjaro - Miles Davis - Columbia, no date. (18 10 0602), n.d. (Box 34)
  - Liberty records - various artists - D-8000 Sonic Spectrum+, n.d. (Box 34)
  - Soul - Sister Rosetta Tharpe sings gospel favorites - CMC, no date. (8123), n.d. (Box 34)
  - Tchaikowsky - violin concerto in D Maj. - Nuremberg Symphony Orchestra/Maga - CMC, no date. (8S524) (Box 34)
  - Love, Andy - Andy Williams - Columbia, no date. (18 K0 0334) (Box 34)
  - Man of La Mancha - original cast album - Kapp Records, no date. (KTC 85505), n.d. (Box 34)
  - Wagner's Greatest Hits - Columbia, no date. (18 11 0120), n.d. (Box 34)
  - The Sound of Boots - Boots Randolph - Monument, no date. (77) MNM 88099 (Box 34)
  - 101 Strings Play - The Soul of Erin - Audio Spectrum, no date. (EO) ASX 85045, n.d. (Box 34)
  - Clair De Lune - Philadelphia Symphony/Ormandy - Columbia, no date. (18 11 0034) (Box 34)
- Box 35
  - Johnny Mathis All-Time Greatest Hits - Columbia/CBS, 1972. (GA 31345), n.d. (Box 35)
  - Modern Jazz Variety - no info. (418), n.d. (Box 35)
  - Joyous Songs of Christmas - Terry Baxter and his Orchestra - Columbia Musical Treasury - no date. (68 30 0214) (Box 35)
  - Tom Paxton #6 - Elektra, no date. (ET8 4066), n.d. (Box 35)
  - Concert in the Park - Andre Kostelanetz - Columbia, no date. (18 10 0286) (Box 35)
  - 30 Piano Masterpieces - highlights vol. 4 - Columbia Musical Treasury - no date. (68 20 0362), n.d. (Box 35)
  - At Folsom Prison - Johnny Cash - Columbia, no date. (18 10 0404), n.d. (Box 35)
  - Sorcerer's Apprentice - Leonard Bernstein plays for young people - New York Philharmonic - Columbia, no date. (18 11 0052), n.d. (Box 35)
  - 101 strings play Million Seller Themes from the Heart of Tchaikovsky - Audio Spectrum, no date. (EO) ASX 85115, n.d. (Box 35)
  - Bobbie Gentry and Glen Campbell - Capitol, no date. (8XT 2928) (Box 35)
  - And So Hard to Forget - Terry Baxter and His Orchestra & Chorus - Columbia Musical Treasury - no date. (68 19 0074) (Box 35)
  - Truth - Jeff Beck - Epic, no date. (N18 10138), n.d. (Box 35)
  - Enlightened Rogues - The Allman Brothers Band - Capricorn, 1979. (M8N-0218) (Box 35)
  - Best of Hank Williams - vol. 1 - A & M Sales, no date. (329), n.d. (Box 35)
  - True Grit - Billy Vaughn - Paramount, no date. (PA 81080), n.d. (Box 35)
  - When the Tingle Becomes a Chill - Loretta Lynn - MCA, 1976. (MCAT 628) (Box 35)
- Box 36
  - Harmony - Don Williams - ABC, 1976. (S130381) (Box 36)
  - Randy Meisner - Elektra/Asylum, 1978. (ET-8140) (Box 36)
  - The World's Favorite Concertos: Tchaikovsky and Mendelssohn Violin Concertos - Heifetz - RCA, 1972. (R8S-1284) (Box 36)
  - "The Sting" Original Motion Picture Soundtrack - MCA, 1974. (MCT 390) (Box 36)
  - You Had To Be There - Jimmy Buffett - MCA, 1979. (AKT2-1008) (Box 36)
  - Feels So Right - Alabama - RCA, 1981. (AHS1-3930) (Box 36)
  - Patsy Cline's Golden Hits - Patsy Cline - GRT/Everest, no date. (U 8059-5200), n.d. (Box 36)
  - In New Orleans - Al Hirt and Slide Hampton - Altone, no date. (1020) (Box 36)
  - Family Tree - The Staples - Warner Bros., 1977. (M8-064) (Box 36)
  - Over the Rainbow: Original Soundtrack Judy Garland TV show - Judy Garland - Altone, no date. (512-0107) (Box 36)
  - So Many Ways/If The Whole World Stopped Lovin' - Eddy Arnold - GRT/MGM, 1973. (M8130-4878) (Box 36)
  - Who's Gonna Play This Old Piano (Think About It Darlin') - Jerry Lee Lewis - Mercury, 1972. (MC 8-61366) (Box 36)
  - He Walks Beside Me - Elvis - no info. (XC 569), n.d. (Box 36)
  - Cooper Brothers - Capricorn Records, 1978. (M8N-0206) (Box 36)
  - Out of the Blue - Electric Light Orchestra - Jet Records, 1977. (JT-EA823-L2) (Box 36)
  - Close To You - Johnny Mathis - Columbia, no date. (LEA 10188), n.d. (Box 36)
  - The Andrews Sisters in Over Here! Original Cast Recording - Columbia, 1974. (KSA 32961) (Box 36)
- Box 37
  - 50 Years of Broadway Music, Cartridge One - The World's Greatest Orchestras and Vocalists - Musicor Records, 1977. (8T-MU303801-1) (Box 37)
  - 20 Bluegrass Originals "Hymns" - Gusto Records, 1978. (GD8-5030X) (Box 37)
  - The Happiness of Having You - Charlie Pride - UPC/Pyramid Communications, 1975. (Box 37)
  - Fantasy - Aquarian Dream - Elektra/Asylum, 1978. (ET-8152) (Box 37)
  - Banjo in the Hills - Stanley Brothers - Starday, no date. (KLP-872), n.d. (Box 37)
  - Operatic Duets - Sutherland and Pavarotti - London/Deca, 1977. (OS8 26449) (Box 37)
  - My Favorite Encores - Van Cliburn - RCA, 1971. (R8S-1171) (Box 37)
  - Natural Progressions - The Bernie Leadon/Michael Georgiades Band - Elektra/Asylum, 1977. (ET-81107) (Box 37)
  - Marty Robbins Greatest Hits Vol. III - Marty Robbins - no info. (528), n.d. (Box 37)